let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What is the correct syntax of web address?",
    answer: "scheme://prefix.domain:port/path/filename",
    options: [
      "port://domain.filenmae:path/scheme/prefix",
      "prefix://scheme.port:domain/filename/path",
      "path://prefix.port:domain/filename/scheme",
      "scheme://prefix.domain:port/path/filename"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is not a difference between HTML and XHTML?",
    answer: "Special characters must be escaped using character entities in XHTML unlike HTML",
    options: [
      "Charset in both html and xhtml is “text/html”",
      "Tags and attributes are case-insensitive in HTML but not in XHTML",
      "Special characters must be escaped using character entities in XHTML unlike HTML",
      "Charset in html is “text/html” where as in xhtml it is “application/xml+xhtml”"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which element is used for or styling HTML5 layout?",
    answer: "CSS",
    options: [
      "CSS",
      "jQuery",
      "JavaScript",
      "PHP"
     
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 4,
    question: "What will be the output of the following JavaScript code? // JavaScript Comparison Operators   function compare()  {  int num=2;  char b=2;  if(a==b)      return true; else   return false;  }",
    answer: "true",
    options: [
      "false",
      "true",
      "compilation error",
      "runtime error"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "Which of the following explains correctly what happens when a JavaScript program is developed on a Unix Machine?",
      answer: "will work perfectly well on a Windows Machine",
      options: [
        "will work perfectly well on a Windows Machine",
        "will be displayed as JavaScript text on the browser",
        "will throw errors and exceptions",
        "must be restricted to a Unix Machine only"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What will be the result or type of error if p is not defined in the following JavaScript code snippet?     console.log(p)",
    answer: "Reference Error",
    options: [
      "Value not found Error",
      "Reference Error",
      "Null",
      "Zero",
  ]
},
{
  numb: 7,
  question: "Which of the following is the property that is triggered in response to JS errors?",
  answer: "onerror",
  options: [
    "onclick",
    "onerror",
    "onmessage",
    "onexception",
]
},
{
  numb: 8,
  question: "In jQuery all the elements are selected by writing ____",
  answer: "$(“*”)",
  options: [
    "$(this)",
    "$(“:button”)",
    "$(“*”)",
    "$(“.class_name”)"
]
},
{
  numb: 9,
  question: "hover() method is the combination of ____",
  answer: "mouseleave() and mouseenter()",
  options: [
    "mouseleave() and mouseenter()",
    "mousedown() and mouseenter()",
    "mouseup() and mousedown()",
    "mouseleave() and mousedown()"
]
},
{
  numb: 10,
  question: "Which method is not for traversing DOM tree sideways?",
  answer: "parent()",
  options: [ 
    "parent()",
    "siblings()",
    "prev()",
    "nextAll()"
]
},

];
